{
    "sold_to_code": "70000801",
    "requested_for_telephone_number": "",
    "request_for_is_vip": "false",
    "reference_number_one": "(RARS) Task - for organisation unit EC-SURE",
    "quantity": "1",
    "item_supplier_part_number": "true",
    "item_shell_part_number": "true",
    "info_previous": "true",
    "duration": "",
    "due_date": "",
    "catalog_version": "42a72ee7c3c81a50b9105d55e001314f",
    "catalog_item_description": "<p>This Catalog item needs to be submitted for requests related to Energy Components for Azure Oracle Database.</p>\n<p>UAM - Assistance on EC AZURE DB requests like - DB user account creation - individual and functional account, password reset, account unlock, modify user access.</p>\n<p><span style=\"font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: 8pt;\">Database Related - Assistance on EC AZURE DB - Request to generate AWR report, Health checks post patch upgrade, Database profile/Role update, Change - Memory, RAM, SGA/PGA/database back up/dump etc.</span></p>",
    "ice4u_source_id": "42a72ee7c3c81a50b9105d55e001314f",
    "ice4u_target_id": "",
    "requested_for_name": "Manoj Krishnamoorthi (INMKS9)",
    "requested_for_email": "Manoj.Krishnamoorthi@shell.com",
    "requested_for_account_name": "Manoj.Krishnamoorthi",
    "requested_for_first_name": "Manoj",
    "opened_by_email": "Jyothis.John@shell.com",
    "correlation_id": "",
    "requested_for_id": "INMKS9",
    "requested_for_location_code": "SBOBNG/BNG-ECO",
    "opened_at": "2024-08-22 09:50:04",
    "task_number": "SCTASK10546844",
    "opened_by_name": "Jyothis John (INJJON)",
    "opened_by_id": "INJJON",
    "task_description": "(RARS) Task - for organisation unit EC-SURE",
    "requested_item_number": "RITM6299680",
    "requested_for_last_name": "Krishnamoorthi",
    "task_short_description": "(RARS) Task - for organisation unit EC-SURE",
    "catalog_item_name": "Energy Components AZURE - Oracle Database Services",
    "variables": [
      {
        "name": "requested_for",
        "question": "Open on behalf of this user",
        "answer": "Manoj Krishnamoorthi (INMKS9)"
      },
      {
        "name": "estimated_delivery_date",
        "question": "Estimated Delivery Date",
        "answer": "2024-09-02 08:05:36"
      },
      {
        "name": "business_justification",
        "question": "Provide the Business Justification",
        "answer": "Create user account for non-support user"
      },
      {
        "name": "calc_estimated_delivery_date",
        "question": "Calculated Estimated Delivery Date ",
        "answer": "2024-09-02 08:05:36"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_type_of_requests",
        "question": "Type of Requests",
        "answer": "User Access Management (UAM)"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_account_type",
        "question": "Account Type",
        "answer": "Individual"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_2nd_line_support",
        "question": "Part of Energy Components 2nd Line Support Team",
        "answer": "No"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_request_for",
        "question": "Request For",
        "answer": "Add"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_role",
        "question": "Role",
        "answer": "undefined"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_app_read_role_read_only",
        "question": "App Read Role (Read Only Access)",
        "answer": "false"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_catalog_role",
        "question": "Catalog Role (System Database Objects)",
        "answer": "false"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_db_audit_role",
        "question": "DB Audit Role (Audit Trial)",
        "answer": "false"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_role_1",
        "question": "Role",
        "answer": "undefined"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_app_read_role_read_only_access_1",
        "question": "App Read Role (Read Only Access)",
        "answer": "true"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_catalog_role_1",
        "question": "Catalog Role (System Database Objects)",
        "answer": "true"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_operating_environment",
        "question": "Operating Environment",
        "answer": "undefined"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_production",
        "question": "Production",
        "answer": "false"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_acceptance",
        "question": "Acceptance",
        "answer": "false"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_test",
        "question": "Test",
        "answer": "true"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_organisational_unit",
        "question": "Organisational Unit",
        "answer": "EC-SURE"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_request_type",
        "question": "Request Type",
        "answer": "undefined"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_password_reset",
        "question": "Password reset",
        "answer": "false"
      },
      {
        "name": "sh_account_unlock",
        "question": "Account Unlock",
        "answer": "false"
      }
    ],
    "snow_variables": {
      "requested_for": "Manoj Krishnamoorthi (INMKS9)",
      "estimated_delivery_date": "2024-09-02 08:05:36",
      "business_justification": "Create user account for non-support user",
      "calc_estimated_delivery_date": "2024-09-02 08:05:36",
      "sh_type_of_requests": "User Access Management (UAM)",
      "sh_account_type": "Individual",
      "sh_2nd_line_support": "No",
      "sh_request_for": "Add",
      "sh_role": "undefined",
      "sh_app_read_role_read_only": "false",
      "sh_catalog_role": "false",
      "sh_db_audit_role": "false",
      "sh_role_1": "undefined",
      "sh_app_read_role_read_only_access_1": "true",
      "sh_catalog_role_1": "true",
      "sh_operating_environment": "undefined",
      "sh_production": "false",
      "sh_acceptance": "false",
      "sh_test": "true",
      "sh_organisational_unit": "EC-SURE",
      "sh_request_type": "undefined",
      "sh_password_reset": "false",
      "sh_account_unlock": "false"
    }
  }